mybrighthouse.com 2015-12-22

# Online Services Privacy Policy

Updated May 2014

Bright House Networks is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to your use of our publicly available websites, mobile sites, applications, and/or other services provided by Bright House Networks that link to this Privacy Policy (“Online Services”). You should also see our [Online Services User Agreement](http://brighthouse.com/policies/policies/online-services-user-agreement.html) (“User Agreement”) for other information concerning your use of our Online Services. We encourage you to read this Policy and call us with any questions. By using our Online Services, you accept both this Policy and the User Agreement.

This Privacy Policy does not govern Bright House’s treatment of information it collects, uses or discloses other than through the Online Services. This Policy does not cover information about you that is collected by Bright House Networks in connection with the provision of our cable television services, high-speed Internet services, and phone services. If you are a customer of BHN, please refer to the Bright House Customer Privacy Notice at [www.brighthouse.com](http://www.brighthouse.com/).

We may modify this Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall become effective immediately upon posting. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this site and this Privacy Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications. If you find the changes unacceptable, do not use the Online Services. If you continue to use the Online Services following notice of the changes, we will consider that to be your acceptance of and consent to the changes.

When we use the terms “Bright House,” “BHN,” “we,” “us” or “our,” we mean Bright House Networks, LLC and the family of companies we own or control. The term “you” refers to you as a user to one or more of the Online Services.

**Information We Collect**

**Policy** — We collect two types of information through our Online Services: personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. It is our policy to collect only the personally identifiable information that we need to provide the Online Services with the quality you desire and deserve.

Personally identifiable information identifies you specifically, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, telephone and fax numbers, and other personally identifying information.

Non-personally identifiable information does not by itself identify a specific individual. This information may include Uniform Resource Locators (“URLs”), demographic information, browser type, and/or your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.

**Online Services Visitors** — When you access our Online Services, we automatically collect access log information about your visit, including information such as the Internet Protocol addresses assigned (numbers assigned to your computer while online), bandwidth used, system and connection performance, browsers used, dates and times of access, and Internet resource requests, including requests to access web pages.

**Online Services Registrants** — In visiting our Online Services, if you register with us or participate in a contest, survey or online transaction, we may ask for certain personally identifiable information. When we ask you for such information, we will tell you how it will be used and you may elect not to participate. When ordering products or services via the Online Services, you may also be asked to provide payment information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

**Cookies and Online Advertising** — We may use “cookies” or similar tools, such as web beacons or tracking pixels, to collect information about your visit to our Online Services and to manage information concerning your preferences. Such tools are small computer code added to files on your computer as a record of its visit and can be used to note information about your visit, such as your type of web browser, operating system and Internet Protocol address, to better tailor the Online Services for you. They can also be used to recognize you when you log in as a registered user or as a repeat visitor. This allows us to tailor the Online Services by remembering you and any options you select. We may share non-personal information obtained from various kinds of cookies with vendors, advertisers and others. You can control what cookies are accepted by your computer through the settings on your web browser or by deleting them from your files. Doing so, however, may limit the personalization available to you. Because a “Do Not Track” protocol has not yet been finalized, Bright House Networks’ information collection and disclosure practices, and the choices that we provide to consumers, will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.

We use a third party provider to place our internet ads. The provider uses “pixel tags,” an industry standard technology used by most major websites to collect anonymous information about your visits to our site and your interaction with our products and services. The provider may also use information about your visits to this and other sites to target advertisements for merchandise and services and to gauge the effectiveness of advertisements. No personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, phone number or email address, is collected or used in this process. If you would like more information about this practice and your option to not have this anonymous information used by our third party provider, please visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>.

**Advertisers and Other Websites** — Third-party ad serving companies and other unaffiliated advertisers may also display advertisements on our websites. As part of their service, they may place a separate cookie on your computer or utilize other means, such as, web beacons, clear GIFs, pixel tags or other similar technologies, to collect non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address, browser type, the server your computer is logged onto, the area code and zip code associated with your server, and whether you responded to a particular advertisement. We do not control the privacy policies of advertisers or of websites you may link to from our Online Services or by using our services. You should review their websites for questions about their Internet security and privacy, and we have no responsibility or liability in connection therewith. To find out more about third party advertising and whether certain opt-outs are available, visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

**Use and Sharing**

**Use Policy** — We consider any personally identifiable information we receive about you to be confidential, and it is our policy to use it only in providing our Online Services. We may also use such information in dealing with fraud and unauthorized use of our services.

**Aggregate Information** — We use aggregate information about our Online Service visitors for a variety of purposes. Such aggregate information does not contain personally identifiable information. We may share such aggregate and related demographic information with third parties.

**Sharing Policy** — It is our overall policy not to disclose your personally identifiable information to others outside of BHN and our affiliates, vendors and business partners without your prior consent. We do not sell or provide your personal information to parties unconnected with the services we provide without your permission.

**Special Exceptions** — We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information in our possession if we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to: (1) comply with the law or legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights or property or those of others; (3) respond to fraud, abuse or unauthorized use of our services; (4) enforce our User Agreement, or Acceptable Use Policy; or (5) act in an emergency to protect your safety or that of another.

**Third Parties** — We sometimes use affiliates, vendors or third party partners in association with our Online Services and may provide personally identifiable information about users for such purposes. In providing such information, we require that the outside party maintain at least the same level of confidentiality that we maintain for such information. In addition, any use by the vendor or third party may not exceed that needed to provide its service.

**Internet Security**

**Taking Proper Precautions** — We take such actions as are necessary to prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information by a person other than you or us. We use security and encryption technologies to secure certain sensitive personally identifiable information we collect through the Online Services. We cannot guarantee, however, that these practices will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use, or disclose personally identifiable information. Maintaining the security of your own personal computer is an important part of protecting your own privacy and of helping us protect our network and our Online Services. You should use and update regularly your antivirus software, firewall and your operating system to prevent unauthorized access by others and harm from various forms of viruses. Persons with questionable intent may use the Internet or email to pose as someone you trust or do business with. You should always be sure who you are dealing with before responding with personal information.

**Access by Others** — It is possible for use of the Internet to be accessed or intercepted by third parties. Moreover, since we cannot control Web sites or Internet services operated by third parties, we recommend that you review the terms of service and privacy policies of those Web sites and services.

**Spam**

Bright House Networks works hard to prevent and to block spam and we encourage your help by preventing unauthorized access to your computer. The law permits companies like BHN to use email to send transactional or relationship messages, such as in confirming that a service has been established or providing information regarding changes in service. If you prefer, you may opt-out of marketing messages we may send by notifying us in response to any you may receive.

**Children’s Privacy**

Our Online Services are not directed at, or intended for use by, children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide any personal information on our websites. Children should always get permission from a parent or guardian before sending personal information over the Internet. If you believe your child may have provided us with personal information, [contact us](http://brighthouse.com/policies/policies/online-services-user-agreement.html) and we will delete the information. You can find more information about protecting children’s privacy by contacting the FTC or viewing its website at [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy notice, we encourage you to [contact us](http://brighthouse.com/support/contact.html) or please call one of our [Business Offices](http://brighthouse.com/support/contact.html).

**California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights**

California law entitles our California customers to request additional information from a business which shares personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties, for their own direct marketing purposes. We may share personally identifiable information with some same-branded affiliates, however, for those affiliates’ direct marketing purposes. If you contact us, we will provide you with the names and addresses of our same-branded affiliates in California and a list of personally identifiable information that we may have shared with them.
